Reza Tanakizadeh

☑ reza.tz780210@gmail.com ♀ Iran 🛗 30 Apr 1999 📞 09015268842 in rezatz

mertz1999 Nonline CV

PROFILE

Two years immersed in machine learning and computer vision, tackling advanced challenges in industry and academia. Proficient in Python, PyTorch, Scikit-Learn, Pandas, Numpy, alongside visualization tools like Streamlit, Matplotlib, and Seaborn. Familiar with deploying solutions using Linux, FastAPI and other key tools.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Computer vision Enginner (Remote)

Sep 2022 – present | Australia, Sydney

DeepMeds &

Top Achievements/Task:

- Gathering and training large-scale image based datasets for object-detection, image-segmentation and classification problems with cutting edge models.
- Using Generative models in medical image
- Image-processing solutions for running some algorithms in real-time.
- Training models for time-series data like EEG signals.

Computer Vision Engineer + Internship

Jan 2022 – Jun 2022 | Terhan, Iran

Nove

Top Achievements/Tasks:

- Using Image processing method (OpenCV) to to solve template matching problem and creating new template matching for more accuracy.
- Satellite image processing to extract information.
- learning to work with pre-trained yolo models and segmentation problems.

Teaching Assistant

Dec 2020 – Apr 2021 | Tehran, Iran

Iran Broadcasting university ≥

• Digital Electronics Teaching Assistant (Winter2020)

OTHER PROJECTS

Volleyball video ball detection and make 3D trajectory *∂*

We used the TrackNet model and modified and train it with gethered data. For the I used 3D computer vision methods and algorithms to convert 2D points into 3D points.

Ball detectio model (TrackNet) ∅ and 3D trajectory mapping ∅

Depth estimation based on car and it's lights positions

This project was an implementation of (A New Approach To Estimate Depth Of Cars Using A Monocular Image ∅) paper.

Macular edema segmentation with DeepLab model *∂*

The DeepLab model was implemented and trained on a gathered dataset, achieving an accuracy of 87%.

AWARDS

1'st place in the Rahneshan competitions

Mar 2022

Iran National Elites Foundation

Design a DOA estimation technique based on deep-learning models. This work was done by a team of 4 memeber that each member worked on an specific part, including deep learning implementation, Simulink model and design antenna.

CERTIFICATES

- Elementary Data Science ${\mathscr Q}$
- Self-Driving Car Specialization (Coursera)
- Ai for Medicine (Coursera)

- Machine learning (Quera)
- Deep Learning Specialization (Coursera)

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Electrical engineeing

Iran Broadcasting University

Sep 2017 – Sep 2021 | Tehran, Iran